englishharmony.com 2013-12-30

# English Harmony Privacy Policy | English Harmony

Share this article with your friends!

 **Privacy Policy**

I have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate my firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with this web site. I hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. The following discloses my information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

**I recognize the importance of protecting your privacy** and my policy is designed to assist you in understanding how I collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide to me and to assist you in making informed decisions when using my site. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and my customers’ needs.

**What Information Do I Collect?** **  
** When you visit this web site you may provide me with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse my Web site.

**1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide**

**Registration Information**  
When you register for any of my products, services or newsletters you will provide me information about yourself:  
-Name  
-Email address

**Email Information**  
If you choose to correspond with me through email, I may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and my responses. I provide the same protections for these electronic communications that I employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**2\. Web Site Use Information**  
Similar to other commercial Web sites, my Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and web server log files to collect information about how my Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at my Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after my Web site.

**How Do I Use the Information That You Provide to Me?**

Broadly speaking, I use personal information for purposes of administering my business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to monitor the use of the service, my marketing and promotional efforts and improve my content and service offerings, and customize my site’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve my site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.

Occasionally, I may also use the information I collect to notify you about important changes to my Website, new services, and special offers I think you will find valuable. You may notify me at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing me at the link provided on the newsletter.

**What Are Cookies?**  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of my site will not function as effectively when viewed by the users. **A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.**

**How Do I Use Information I Collect from Cookies?**  
As you visit and browse my Web site, the site uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, I also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with my Web server’s log files, allow me to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting my Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps me gather feedback to constantly improve my Web site and better serve my clients. Cookies do not allow me to gather any personal information about you and I do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to me in your cookies.

**IP Addresses**  
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by my web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Sharing and Selling Information**  
I  **do not** share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that I collect online and maintain in my database by emailing me at the usual address.

**What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?  
**I may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when I, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of my legal rights.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to My Web Site?**  
I’m not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from my Web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of my Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from my Website to another web site, my Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including web sites, which have a link on my Website, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**  
By using my Web site you consent to my collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. I reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

_**My Commitment To Data Security:**_

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, I have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information I collect online.

**Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out  
**This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing I will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

**A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use my services unsupervised and I ask that children (under the age of 14) do not submit any personal information to me. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

**Acquisition or Changes in Ownership**

In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

**Policy Modifications** **  
** I may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, I will email users who have given me permission to do so. I will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, I will not use the personal information you have submitted to me under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

**Regards,**

**Robby Kukurs**

Share this article with your friends!
